Cristian Alejandro Zendejas

1410 Mary St. N

St. Paul, MN 55119

651-239-3920 Czend371@gmail.com

Summary:

Graduate from Century College. Graduated with an Associate's in Arts degree in 2014. Served in the United States Marine Corps from 2015-2019. Currently attending University of Minnesota's coding bootcamp and will graduate in October of 2019. Great leadership skills as well as strong work ethic. Experience working in teams and independently. Qualifications:

- Time management
- Monitoring
- Multitasking
- Critical Thinking
- Coordination
- Complex Problem Solving
- Attention to detail
- Collaboration/teamwork
- Ability to work under pressure
- Great interpersonal Communication
- Secret Clearance

Programming Languages

HTML/CSS

Javascript

Node.js

Experience

Corporal (U.S. Marine Corps), Camp Lejeune, NC Jan 2015-Jan 2019

Supervised and facilitated training for 10 employees. This lead to improved job performance and overall provided a better product to the company.

Led small 4-5 group projects in order accomplish a task within a time limit.

Made decisions and implemented plans that has saved the company time and money.

Managed thousands of dollars' worth of radio equipment during small and large projects. Awarded Certificate of Commendation.

Security Officer/2nd Shift Supervisor, Guardsmark, Minnetonka, MN Dec 2013-Dec 2014

Supervised and orchestrated post schedules. This led to efficient rotations while maintaining integrity of security.

Reviewed and analyzed video footage of possible accidents/crimes from various company locations both domestic and international. Recorded findings that led to possible arrests and helped find flaws in company security.

Created and managed security badges for personnel that entered the building.

Education

U.S. Marine Corps: Specialized training in leadership, diversity, and communications
Associate in Arts, Century College, Mahtomedi, Minnesota

<u>Awards</u>

Certificate of Commendation (2016) Recognized for tracking and handling of thousands of dollars' worth of radio equipment (a supervisor role) when I was in an entry level role.

Good Conduct Medal (2018) Recognized for exemplary personal and professional conduct.